{
    "id": "b62a3e2c55ca4eb09914c14cd94ac55a",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. you help me with my homework?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………. obey the traffic rules.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "must",
                "ought to",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. do it. (Unwillingness)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not",
                "shall not",
                "cannot"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Unless you are careful, you …………… get into trouble. (Prediction)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The children asked whether they …………….. go for a swim. (Permission)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………… hear music playing in the next room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you work hard, you …………. succeed. (Prediction)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We did all that we …………… (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………… not come. (Possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………. permit this. (Weak possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "might",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………. sacrifice my life for my country. (Determination)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The rattle snake ………….. move very fast. (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………… park here. (Prohibition)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "must",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}